Thirty-four.
Thirty-five.
Thirty-six.
Thirty-seven.
Golo presents
Thirty-eight.
Thirty-nine.
Forty.
Forty-one.
Forty-two.
Wrong.
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
Completely wrong!
That's the end of the registered list.
Your memory is of an instant you
glimpsed just before losing consciousness.
Please go over it slowly one more time.
Let us start from the beginning-
I've said it many times already.
There is no way it could be on this list.
I was attacked by a-
Talking about the monster again?
Give the scene a good sweep.
I can go with you if you like.
Based on your statement,
we conducted a thorough search of the
memory of your home's surveillance unit
as well as your Entourage's,
but there was nothing.
This is a conspiracy!
The Security Bureau deleted
inconvenient data beforehand, didn't they?!
This is a treasonous act against the Information Bureau-
no, the Administration Bureau!
Reporting increased heart rate
in your vital signs.
Mind your own business!
Please remember your station and be mindful of your well-being.
You are the Administrator's grandchild.
What a snake.
Your very birth
makes you an ideal target for refugees
whose emotions are not fully under control.
For instance,
the one who was found collapsed near your home last night-
this man.
What were you doing there?
With legitimate examples and situations in mind,
restate your explanation.
I received information that an infected autoreiv had been spotted.
Unable to verify information.
But... it's true.
If you would search the facility's data records...
Vincent Law.
There are reports of him developing feelings for you as well.
What about the possibility that the
crime was committed by a stalker?
A stalker?
As if he has the balls.
This is a waste of time.
Restate from the beginning.
Code number 0724FGARK...
The faces of model citizens...
Faces...
Employee at the AR Control Division...
meditation    confessions of a model citizen
Those of you who are model citizens,
let's throw things away.
Though they may be necessary,
be strong-
And,
they also said they'll prepare a
replacement home for you within six hours.
Then stop by Central Mall.
Stuff like shoes, belts,
pants, shampoo,
conditioner, skincare products, toothbrushes-
I'm gonna buy 'em up.
No, no.
I can understand why you want to let off some steam,
but we have to go to Daedalus' place first.
If you want to show up at the Information Bureau,
they said you'd need your primary care physician's diagnosis.
It's just a scratch.
I'm fine.
It's not just about physical injuries.
Considering what happened,
who knows what mental-
Cut the crap!
That monster from yesterday
wasn't even recorded in your head.
What's wrong?
Re-l, cheer up.
C'mon, your place is in awful
shape. It's like there was an explosion.
It's a miracle that you got off with only that scratch.
I was worried about you, you know.
Getting caught up in something like that...
You're real tough.
So, how's the homicide investigation going?
Well, about that...
Why would I be taken off the case?
We got a memo from the brass.
In other words, considering your injuries...
A scratch like this?
No, the Security Bureau's report stated
that trauma from the incident caused a slight mental issue.
What was it called?
Pseudology.
Sounds like something they'd come up with.
Calm dowm, Re-l.
Your heart rate is-
That's none of your business.
Fine, how would you explain what
happened yesterday at the old Immigration Bureau?
Autoreivs did not leave those marks behind.
Yesterday?
What are you talking about?
Impossible...
Even memories about the investigation were erased?
We request submission of a mental health diagnosis report
by your primary care physician
before you may resume your duties.
You have Dr. Daedalus.
How lucky you are to have the Health
Bureau's chairman as your physician.
The Citizen Health Bureau...
See?
Okay, you'll cheer up once the "prince" gives you a kiss.
I see.
I understand.
I have an appointment, I hope?
He said to come by anytime. C'mon.
Wait.
What's the matter all of a sudden?
Take care.
The Security Bureau's loss of control...
the Information Bureau's silence,
Iggy's manipulation...
Each dot is linked to monsters
and will eventually connect.
Isn't that right,
Grandfather?
It is completely outside of our predicted escape route.
So, even though it ventured into the
immigrant sectors beyond the city limits,
it returned to the city...
So PROXY's target...
must be Re-l after all.
Your statement was within our predictions.
We have completely eliminated any traces
left by PROXY at the site after recording them.
Re-l Mayer has been released from custody as well.
We wouldn't be able to justify further attempts
at buying time to the Administrator anyway.
You may release the immigrants
after the interrogation formalities are over.
They are not suspects.
Confirmed.
Would you like to look at her statement?
No.
However, she is stricken
by temporary mental instability due to the stalker attack,
and can not make a distinction between dreams and reality.
It is a frequent phenomenon among humans.
As insurance, I have arranged to have
her submit a psychiatric diagnosis report
made by her primary care physician
in order to be released from probation.
Beautiful.
Now, no one will believe what she said she saw.
Preserving the secret of PROXY
has the highest priority above all else.
Your will is my command.
Psychological warfare, then?
Administrator's grandchild or not, I will allow no interference.
Then please continue to supervise the PROXY research.
Yes.
Any pain?
I'm fine.
Thank you.
You're way over the top.
In any case, I'm glad you're all right.
If anything ever happens to you,
I...
Way over the top.
I wish you'd believe what I'm saying then.
Suspected of phantastic pseudology?
This isn't going to work.
But listen, Daedalus.
Do you have any idea how I feel?
No one believes me.
I see.
I saw a monster!
With my own eyes.
I'd like to believe you.
So I'd like you to let me look into your mind, just for a little bit.
I'm not being delusional.
Please believe me!
Re-l!
I know what you're trying to say.
Even I
don't know what's real and what's not anymore.
Memory confusion, huh.
It'll take time to put you through diagnosis
and preparations before giving you counselling,
but let's do a brain scan too.
Are you okay with that?
If it's you telling me, Daedalus.
I'll make preparations right away.
"Specimen"?
"Proxy"...
Sorry.
It took longer than we thought.
No,
not a problem.
I'd like to let you see her soon.
She's very cute.
Sure, okay.
I'll go on ahead.
We are ready to leave.
You surprised me.
App, on.
How was it?
I'm physically fine.
Mentally? It'll depend on the report.
Well, to the mall, then!
More importantly, I'd like you to look into something first.
No problem.
Connect to the Central Information Bank.
Connection, complete.
Input keyword: Proxy.
Connection, aborted.
Forced shutdown of Turing function app from speech area.
Unable to acknowledge keyword.
Retry input, or abort?
Just as I'd thought.
App, on.
So, Re-l.
What do you want me to look up?
Don't bother.
What's up with you?
Oh, hang on a second.
You have an emergency call from your grandfather.
He was monitoring Iggy?
It's about yesterday.
Want to put it off until after you finish shopping?
We'll go.
I can't escape him.
We were just talking about you.
I'm sorry.
I apologize for the fact that I ignored your recent summons.
Never mind that.
The issue that should be discussed between us now is-
"PROXY".
A flaw in our operations.
There are times when cooperation with the Security
Bureau is more important than maintaining one's own ego.
What is PROXY?
Re-l,
I won't know what you're trying to say if you keep your silence.
So you'll ignore me?
That's due to certainty, isn't it?
Isn't that right, Grandfather?
If you don't want to give me an answer, that's fine.
Re-l will be assigned to the Administration Bureau.
There will be a hearing.
Hey!
Husserl!
Berkeley!
Don't be so arbitrary!
Lacan!
Derrida!
Grandfather...
Re-l.
Swear that you will no longer take unauthorized action.
Well?
Derrida...
If not,
like Berkeley said,
you will be placed under the
surveillance of the Administration Bureau.
Understood.
Re-l has promised us.
Now, go.
This is...
It's time.
Already?
Is that the report from the research facility?
I will do the rest.
There's no need for that.
I'll put it together soon enough.
Would you arrange for a car instead?
Understood.
There were two PROXIES...
Impossible...
New homes are so nice.
This has a good view too.
Re-l?
Oh, sorry.
Did you say something?
Jeez.
Did something happen with your prince?
Iggy...
You are being watched.
Sorry.
Re-l,
where are you going?
I'm going to get a change of clothes.
"Get"?
I think your place's still under the Security Bureau's jurisdiction.
I want a change.
I've been wearing this since yesterday.
I'll have trouble finding things to wear from tomorrow on.
Why don't you use this opportunity
to get yourself a brand-new wardrobe?
Why would you have any reason to go there?
Grandfather...
So not only does he watch me
but he also wishes to manipulate me.
Well...
I don't see anything I want in the new line-up.
What?
You were saying this morning that you
were going to go on a shopping spree.
Wait.
I know a good place.
Let's go there together.
How about this?
The colors are perfect for this season too...
Re-l?
That's...
Chief!
Please issue commands to the Security Bureau.
Request an emergency sortie of armed autoreivs.
Seal off Yoslis Park and the surrounding sectors.
Use barriers.
Understood.
Report.
Forty-two adult and infant deaths.
Forty-eight wounded.
All the citizens within the mall were secured in isolation facilities.
What about the specimen?
It has breached the barriers
and is still at large.
This is surveillance footage from sector N-31.
The specimen is estimated to have
already reached the lower sectors.
It wasn't a dream...
It was real.
It's Papa!
Damn!
He...
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
The sages suffer from exhaustion.
The clues intersect.
The whereabouts of the doll who fails to respond to a summons.
As the chase draws to a close...
meditation  leap into a void
the portal to utopia opens.